giftsandguests.com 2005-04-03

# Privacy Statement :: Namesco Limited Domain Names, Hosting, Dedicated Server Solutions and Broadband

  * > Customer Login
  * Domain Names
  * Email Packages
  * Web Hosting
  * Dedicated Servers
  * Search Engine Submit
  * Web Development
  * Internet Access
  * Help and Support
  * Latest News
  * About Us
  * Contact Us
  * Price List

|   
---  
| 

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for Namesco Limited.

This web site agrees to notify you of: 

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the web site 
  2. The organization collecting the information 
  3. How the information is used 
  4. With whom the information may be shared 
  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information 
  6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Namesco Limited control 
  7. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should contact us

Information Collection and Use 

Namesco Limited is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Namesco Limited collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

Order 

We request information from the user on our registration, order and payment forms. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. 

Cookies 

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site and is encrypted so cannot be read by any other website. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. It will also terminate once a period of time has elapsed since first using the site. 

We only use cookies for your convenience; for instance, to prevent the user from having to re-enter shopping cart information. If a user rejects the cookie, ordering functionality for the user will be affected. 

Log Files 

We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

Sharing 

We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

We use a credit card processing company to bill users for services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

Links 

This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we [Namesco Limited] are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site. 

Security 

This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our accounting staff or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. 

Correction/Updating Personal Information: 

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your post code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. 

Choice/Opt-out 

If you use this site to purchase services you may occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications on our order form. 

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email, or by contacting us directly. 

Users of our site are notified when their information is being collected or used by any third parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an third party, or not. 

Notification of Changes 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

|  |
